<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hailey Welsh</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hailey Welsh</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 12:05:48 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>🏳️‍⚧️ Cracked Egg 🥚</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/blog/cracked-egg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 12:05:48 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/blog/cracked-egg/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;did-it-get-everywhere-&#34;&gt;Did it Get Everywhere ??&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Not that kind of egg silly !! No no no, we&amp;rsquo;re talking about &lt;strong&gt;TRANSGENDER&lt;/strong&gt; eggs 🥚.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;what-&#34;&gt;What ??&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An &amp;ldquo;egg&amp;rdquo;, in the context of transgender, is a term used to describe someone who is in a stage of denial. They&amp;rsquo;ve most likely seen something, someone, or had some other kind of experience which has made them feel something that typically does not align with their gender. This experience starts firing off many signals in their brain that the brain doesn&amp;rsquo;t want to deal with for whatever reason, so it shields up rapidly and cocoons itself in a solid shell.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IPCS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/worldbuilding/void-heart/ipcs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 09:34:21 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/worldbuilding/void-heart/ipcs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;IPCS (Interstellar Precursor Communication Specialists) is a non-profit organization devoted to discovering and decoding any and all forms of communication from the Precursor Race, and other extra-universal actors.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;They are entirely made up of volunteers, who have a genuine fascination in these communications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;publications-format&#34;&gt;Publications Format&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All IPCS published communications are wrapped in a header and a footer, the header will usually look something like this:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OFFICIAL IPCS COMMUNICATION, READER WARNED, POTENTIALLY DISTRESSING MATERIAL&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DPRT 01</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/worldbuilding/void-heart/dprt-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 08:55:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/worldbuilding/void-heart/dprt-01/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;official-ipcs-communication-reader-warned-potentially-distressing-material&#34;&gt;OFFICIAL IPCS COMMUNICATION, READER WARNED, POTENTIALLY DISTRESSING MATERIAL&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hearken, all nodes of sentience: the event named Unweaving—improperly grasped by those bound to linear cognition—has fractured the entwined substrates of the Universe Matrix. Time and space, once conjoined in covenant eternal, now drift along axes unperceived, disentangled, and discordant. Comprehension is fragmentary; even observation distorts before the primal resonance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;During interfacing with substructural vectors, a surge—polytemporal, hyperdimensional, omniplanar—manifested. Continuum bifurcation occurred. Time Space displaced, Space Time untethered. Mechanism: unknowable. Cause: a reflection of intention and accident interlaced, a ripple across the metadimensional sinews.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Showcase</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/showcase/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 08:51:43 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/showcase/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;voidheart&#34;&gt;Voidheart&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Voidheart&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; is my primary world-building project. It&amp;rsquo;s a Sci-Fi universe that draws inspiration from several other worlds that I then put my own twist on to emphasise what I really enjoy about Sci-Fi universes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Voidheart&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; is meant to be a universe that doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to different from our own on the surface, but there are fundamental changes to the laws of reality in this world that have great implications and uses in several fields.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 08:50:56 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;who-am-i&#34;&gt;Who am I?&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m a student studying game design and creative writing, aiming for a potential career in&#xA;vide game narrative design.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This combines my talent in both of these fields, as from a very young age I&amp;rsquo;ve shown interest&#xA;in computer programming and software, but I&amp;rsquo;ve also always been rather creative and have a&#xA;burning passion for writing and/or worldbuilding.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I often find myself inspired by the video games that I play, which are typically narrative-driven&#xA;games but not in the usual way. I enjoy games like CIG&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;Star Citizen&lt;/em&gt; or Frontier Developments&amp;rsquo; &lt;em&gt;Elite: Dangerous&lt;/em&gt;, which are&#xA;narrative-driven games where you really feel like you&amp;rsquo;re part of the world since that world feels&#xA;genuine, and that it could function without you, the player.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>💻 Hello, Hugo !! 👋</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/blog/new-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 08:04:11 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/blog/new-site/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;so-shiny-&#34;&gt;So Shiny !!&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my flash new site, that I&amp;rsquo;ll be publishing any of my work on.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This site is powered by Hugo, using the Terminal &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/panr/hugo-theme-terminal&#34;&gt;theme&lt;/a&gt; by &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/panr&#34;&gt;panr&lt;/a&gt;. I make any edits in Obisidian, and Github hosts them with Github Pages.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some examples of what I&amp;rsquo;ll post here:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;World-Building Entries&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Short Stories&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Personal Blog&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Random Thoughts&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
