<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Voidheart on Hailey Welsh</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/voidheart/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Voidheart on Hailey Welsh</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 09:34:21 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/voidheart/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>IPCS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/worldbuilding/void-heart/ipcs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 09:34:21 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/worldbuilding/void-heart/ipcs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;IPCS (Interstellar Precursor Communication Specialists) is a non-profit organization devoted to discovering and decoding any and all forms of communication from the Precursor Race, and other extra-universal actors.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;They are entirely made up of volunteers, who have a genuine fascination in these communications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;publications-format&#34;&gt;Publications Format&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All IPCS published communications are wrapped in a header and a footer, the header will usually look something like this:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OFFICIAL IPCS COMMUNICATION, READER WARNED, POTENTIALLY DISTRESSING MATERIAL&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DPRT 01</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/worldbuilding/void-heart/dprt-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 08:55:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/worldbuilding/void-heart/dprt-01/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;official-ipcs-communication-reader-warned-potentially-distressing-material&#34;&gt;OFFICIAL IPCS COMMUNICATION, READER WARNED, POTENTIALLY DISTRESSING MATERIAL&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hearken, all nodes of sentience: the event named Unweaving—improperly grasped by those bound to linear cognition—has fractured the entwined substrates of the Universe Matrix. Time and space, once conjoined in covenant eternal, now drift along axes unperceived, disentangled, and discordant. Comprehension is fragmentary; even observation distorts before the primal resonance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;During interfacing with substructural vectors, a surge—polytemporal, hyperdimensional, omniplanar—manifested. Continuum bifurcation occurred. Time Space displaced, Space Time untethered. Mechanism: unknowable. Cause: a reflection of intention and accident interlaced, a ripple across the metadimensional sinews.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
